<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" ?>

<profile>
    <documentation>
        <p>
            Dependencies can be used between Services and Entities, they
            won't need any stereotype assigned to them. These dependencies
            are used to reference an entity from another entity or service,
            or to reference a service from an entity or another service.
        </p>
        <p>
            Entity query operations (i.e. finders) can be denoted by setting the
            query flag on the modeled operation to true
            (they do not require any stereotypes).
        </p>
        <p>
            Actors represent roles within your model. To designate that a role
            has access to a given service you must draw a dependency from an Actor
            to the
            <a href="Service"><![CDATA[<<Service>>]]></a>. To designate the
            role has access to to a given operation, you must draw a dependency from
            an Actor to the operation.
        </p>
    </documentation>
    <elements>
        <elementGroup name="Stereotypes">
            
            <element name="DOCUMENT">
                <documentation>
                    Denotes a class is representing an MongoDB POJO.
                </documentation>
                <value>Document</value>
                <appliedOnElement>class</appliedOnElement>
            </element>
            
            <element name="ENTITY">
                <documentation>
                    Denotes a class is representing an MongoDB POJO. This will instruct the cartridge to generate
                    an <code>.hbm.xml</code> descriptor and the corresponding class from it.
                </documentation>
                <value>Entity</value>
                <appliedOnElement>class</appliedOnElement>
            </element>
            
            <element name="SERVICE">
                <documentation>
                    Denotes a class is representing an EJB session bean that is supposed to be used as a facade
                    for a set of entities.
                </documentation>
                <value>Service</value>
                <appliedOnElement>class</appliedOnElement>
            </element>
            
            <element name="ENUMERATION">
                <documentation>
                    This class will instruct the generation of a type-safe enumeration class. The class implements the
                    required MongoDB interface to be able to be persisted. That way it is possible for Entities to
                    use this enumeration type for their attributes.
                </documentation>
                <value>Enumeration</value>
                <appliedOnElement>class</appliedOnElement>
            </element>
        </elementGroup>
        <elementGroup name="Tagged Values">
            <element name="HIBERNATE_INVERSE">
                <value>@andromda.hibernate.inverse</value>
            </element>
            <element name="MONGODB_ASSOCIATION_TYPE">
                <value>@andromda.mongodb.association.type</value>
            </element>
        </elementGroup>
    </elements>
</profile>
